<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<hea>
<title> Personal Website</title>
</head>
<body>
<h2>My Picture</h2>
<img src="https://scontent.fsyd5-1.fna.fbcdn.net/v/t1.0-9/70268844_1548494298622216_4447466367611830272_o.jpg?_nc_cat=103&ccb=1-3&_nc_sid=730e14&_nc_ohc=y8iCfvljnHcAX-vRHVk&_nc_ht=scontent.fsyd5-1.fna&oh=0c119874e358251a31438b5cc6a7623a&oe=607CB81D" alt="My Picture" width="300" height="300">

<h1 style="color:Tomato;">Personal information</h1>
<p style="color:DodgerBlue;">Name: Suruchi Shrestha</p>                                            
<p style="color:DodgerBlue;">Student no: s3910962</p> 
<p style="color:DodgerBlue;"><a href="mail to: s3910962@student.rmit.edu.au">send email</a></p> 
<p style="color:DodgerBlue;">Background information: I am currently opting to fulfill the Master’s Degree in teaching. IT has been playing an influencing role for the students as well as teachers that assist in better understanding. I have been interested in taking up the ICT course which would help me in future growth.</p> 
<p style="color:DodgerBlue;">Education to date: Graduated with Bachelor of professional Accounting on 2018.</p> 
<p style="color:DodgerBlue;">Languages spoken: English, Nepali, Hindi</p>
<p style="color:DodgerBlue;">Hobby: Interested in reading books and exploring new places</p>

<h2 style="color:Tomato;">Interest in IT</h2>
<p>It is evident from my information shared in the above section that I do not have any background in IT. This course is taken up by me as I want to pursue a Master's degree in teaching and currently, ICT is transforming the learning environments.  In this regard, my interest in the course is mainly developed from the point that having knowledge on this would enhance the education quality.<p>
<p>The teachers also need to be further updated with the needed technical skills and thereby enhance the teaching skills. I don't have any experience or background in IT, so it is all about the role of ICT in improving education that compelled me to take up the course. I have taken up admission in RMIT as the university offers the course and prepares for success. During my studies, I will be exploring and learning new concepts, ideas as well as equipping myself with the required knowledge.<p>

<h3 style="color:Tomato;">Ideal Job<h3>

<p>Position description: The job is to boat the information technology teacher and client for this job Catholic school that is located across the inner northern suburbs of Melbourne. The school provides holistic education and would need expertise in junior digital technology and VCE applied to compute.</p> 
<p>Description of skills, qualification, and experience: The position seeks candidates that have knowledge on digital technology, relevant tertiary education, and have professional references. Apart from this, the person should have a work permit in Australia (Lopez et al. 2019). The person should further have teaching qualifications to teach information technology. Besides this, the candidate should also have registration with the Teacher Registration Board of Western Austria.</p>
<p>Current skills and qualification: The person is currently pursuing a Master's degree in Teaching.</p>
<p>Plan for obtaining the skills: After pursuing the degree in teaching with the ICT course, I shall be seeking to get registration in teaching in the board of Western Australia (Cengel et al. 2019). Apart from this, I will be also taking a short-term course on digital technology to further my skills.</p>

<h4 style="color:Tomato;">Personal Profile</h4>
<p>Importance of three tests: The first test talks about the kind of personality exhibited by me which is virtuosos that seeks for exploring everything with cool rationalism as well as spirited curiosity. The personality test also speaks that the decision made by such people stems from a point of practical realism. The second test illustrates the learning style which is Auditory (Schilling et al. 2020). With this learning style, I try to learn things by reading out loud and have an easier time in terms of understanding instructions. The third style illustrates that I am more inclined towards agreeableness, Neuroticism as well as openness.</p> 
<p>Ways in which the tests shall influence behaviour: The tests and assessments have been enlightening and have created an accurate image of my personality in my own mind. This has helped me in analysing the areas that I am lacking and significant improvements in the field of confidence, ways of directing the mental energy as well as the ways in which I would react to the situations.</p>
<p>Team formation based on the test experience: In terms of team formation some of the key qualities such as agreeableness, tactics in the decision making, approach towards work, and openness shall be of great help (Kyllonen and Kell, 2018).</p>

<h5 style="color:Tomato;">Project Idea</h5>
<p style="color:DodgerBlue;">Overview</p>
<p>The project up taken by me is smartphone app development for the learning of students and teachers that will boost the performance parallelly. This would be a quiz app that will be developed using the Android studio for mobile phones and this would help in testing the knowledge of the students. The quiz app shall provide random as well as interactive information that would be self-paced (Faridah et al. 2018). There would be different types of quizzes and users shall choose a matching word, MCQs, and other such. The marks shall be based on provided questions and a second shall be given for answering the question correctly. The quiz app shall further have answers on one word that would make the users easily identifying the answers. The time shall be restricted which would make it more competitive.</p>
<p style="color:DodgerBlue;">Motivation</p>
<p>In the year 2020, the spread of Coronavirus had put people locked in their homes. At that point, the internet played a major role in bringing all activities at a pace that had been stopped due to the virus outbreak. In this situation, from the education perspective, the students and teacher both were intermittently relied on mobile applications for securing knowledge. Moreover, the mobile application generated more than $188.9 billion and is expected to generate $510.39 billion by the end of the year 2022 (Wibawa et al. 2018). The app shall help the users in answering it repeatedly even if the first attempt is wrong. This would encourage the users to play and many users at a time can play. With the app, individuals shall get help for developing positive personalities and improve their attitudes simultaneously.</p>
<p style="color:DodgerBlue;">Description</p>
<p>The quiz application deals with the overall development of the android supported multiple-choice questionnaires examination system. It shall be developed for educational purposes that would allow the MCQs to prepare for various types of exams that shall be conducted on a provincial level (Lone et al. 2019). The key goals of the app are to allow the users to keep on practicing the subjective tests that are majorly conducted for admission as well as recruitments. It shall mainly focus on the computer science fields and comes with three key modules namely verbal, analytical as well as computer science.  Along with this, computer science, as well as the verbal modules, shall further consider subcategories with functionalities such as hint, skip as well as pause. These key functionalities shall be used by the user only once time and this would demonstrate the progress feedback at the time of quiz play and shows the result at the end of the quiz (Şahin et al. 2017). The app allows the users to view the hints for the correct answers, can easily skip the question and these lifelines shall be used only once. The other features such as answering questions, scoring high among the groups similar to the other apps. There would be different modules each with specific functions:</p>

<p>Main screen: It is the starting screen and has two buttons: Start and Instruction</p>
<p>Instruction screen: In the screen containing the instruction description shall act as a guide for the details about the play app. There would be a back button for which the control shall go back to the main screen.</p>
<p>Time setup screen: It shall have three buttons namely categories, time, and back. The categories button shall put the control to the categories screen.</p>
<p>Time screen: This would help in setting up the desired time span for the quiz and the list picker shall be used for the purpose.</p>
<p>Main categories screen: This shall have analytical, verbal as well as computer science to redirect users to the corresponding category (Pauli et al. 2019).</p>
<p>Categories for computer science module: It shall have five buttons namely OS, DBMS, computer Architecture, computer networking as well as a data structure.</p>
<p>Verbal subcategories: It shall consist of eight major buttons namely: spelling, selection of words, analogies, spotting words, antonyms, synonyms as well as word order.</p>
<p>Questionnaire screen: The screen comes with labels that would show feedback, status, and lifelines. </p>
<p>Result screen: It shall be the last screen that would show your scores and maximum scores, as well as another label "correct questions for which the answers were correct. Apart from this, another option Attempt shall be there to show the number of questions that the user attempts.</p>

<p style="color:DodgerBlue;">Tools and technologies</p>
<p>In terms of software, hardware, as well as the other requirements needed for the project completion, is concerned, Android Studio, HTML, and CSS language shall be used for the development of the software. A definite architecture from the technical perspective shall be ended, a technology stack as well as defining the development milestone must be set.  The backend or the server theology to be used shall be Oracle database which would support the functioning of the mobile app</p>
<p>For the front-end development, Java language shall be used which is best for the quiz mobile application. Apart from this, the following are the set of basic material requirements:</p>
<p>Windows 10 laptop</p>
<p>Android smartphone</p>
<p>MIT app inventor</p>

<pstyle="color:DodgerBlue;">Skills required</p>
<p>The key skills needed for the project are majorly based on the set of tools and knowledge that the developer has on it. This App inverter which is an open-source web app for Android is needed (Pechenkina et al. 2017). Apart from this, good knowledge in Java, as well as XML, shall be needed for the UI part. Major libraries shall be needed for creating the programming interfaces that would contain the functions.</p>

<p style="color:DodgerBlue;">Outcome</p>
<p>The applications shall be developed to offer a new range of aspects and perceptions towards learning. This shall act as a ground for self-improvement and the majority of the applications that are available in the market are entertainment-based that fails in contributing towards the enhancement of student learning. The key theme of the quiz app revolves around practicing the test and thereby preparing for computer-related texts.</p>

<p  style="color:DodgerBlue;">Appendix</p>
<p>Links to tests</p>
<p><a href="https://www.truity.com/personality-test/212/result/13177206">Truity.com!</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.16personalities.com/istp-personality">16personalities.com!</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.educationplanner.org/students/self-assessments/learning-styles-">education planner.com!</a></p>
<p><a href="quiz.shtml?event=results&A=12&V=4&T=4">quiz.shtml!</a></p>
</body>

</html>